So in this section, we're going to focus on other AWS AI services, basically all the non-geny AI services.
So before we get into the details of these AWS AI services, I thought it might be a good idea
to give you a quick mental map of how they're structured. So we have the artificial intelligence
and within artificial intelligence, we have machine learning, machine learning focuses on training
AI models using data and there are different ways in which you can train those models
either using supervised learning, unsupervised learning and reinforcement learning. So we're not
going to get into details of these because there's little chance that these are going to be
tested in the exam. Okay, now within machine learning, there's a subset called as neural networks
and deep learning and most of the generative and agent AI services that we have learned till now
are broadly a subset of neural network and deep learning.
Now the second branch of artificial intelligence is computer vision and computer vision focuses
on image processing and video processing. So anything related to image and video processing
is part of the computer vision. From the AWS perspective, the key service in the computer vision
area is Amazon recognition service and we're going to do dive into this service and the next
branch within artificial intelligence is natural language processing and this is focused on
speech and text processing. Now there are a lot of different AWS AI services in this area
and couple of them include Amazon transcribe which converts wise to text and then we have
Amazon poly which does text to wise and there are a lot of AWS services that are focused on
natural language processing and we're going to debave into all of them and then we have robotics
and robotics is more focused on the industrial automation to improve the human productivity.
Now robotics is not part of the exam so in this section we're mainly going to focus on services
related to computer vision and natural language processing. Okay so that's pretty much it from
this lecture I'll see in the next lecture. Thank you.